Nisha Shah

Senior Operations Analyst

Passionate and result driven professional with 5+ years of experience in Electronic Discovery. Seeking a challenging position in reputable organization to expand my learnings, knowledge, and skills while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.



nishashah2104@gmail.com

9851426866

Bangalore, India

linkedin.com/in/nisha-shah

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Operations Analyst EpiqSystems India Pvt Ltd

09/2023 - Present

Job Profile

- Identification, collection, processing and hosting data are the main parts of my current role.
- Working with tools like NUIX, Relativity, RelOne, Epiq Discovery, AWS, FileZilla, FTK and various other internal tools, etc.
- OJT for new joiner from entire APAC team on different workflows/concepts, different e-discovery applications, clarifying doubts
- Handling APAC PMs with multiple queries.
- Point of Contact from the onshore team regarding any sort of update.
- Handling queue and prioritizing multiple projects with short deadlines.

Operations Analyst EpiqSystems India Pvt Ltd

02/2022 - 08/2023

Job Profile

- Identification, collection, processing and hosting data are the main parts of my current role.
- Working with tools like DMX, NUIX, Relativity, Epig Discovery, AWS, FTK and various other internal tools, etc.

Analyst, Data Operations Consilio LLC

04/2021 - 02/2022

Job Profile

- Generate analysis and status reports from SQL databases. Working with tools NUIX, Encase, VeraCrypt, Relativity, AMR, FTK etc.
- Train other team members and new joiners on e-discovery applications, concepts and workflows.
- Prioritize multiple projects with similar deadlines.
- Data mining to generate project reports.

Associate Consultant

Harman Connected Services [Consilio LLC]

08/2018 - 03/2021

Job Profile

- Analyze and format appropriate data from historical and active structured data sources through a variety of different tools and programs in support of the legal department.
- Generate analysis and status reports from SQL databases. Working with tools NUIX, Encase, VeraCrypt, Relativity, AMR, FTK etc.
- Prioritize multiple projects with similar deadlines.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

BTech in Electronics and Communication Engineering with 8.84 DGPA

Surendra Institute of Engineering and Management, Siliguri

08/2013 - 06/2017

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Limited Working Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

